Guide to the David Jacks Papers, 1845-1960
Department of Special Collections
- Margaret Jacks et. al. - Business & Legal (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - 8. 1929, May 20.Resolution of thanks. City of Monterey to L., M. & V. Jacks. Gift $13,000.
  - 9. 1939, Oct. 5.TLS Romie C. Jacks to Lee Jacks.
  - 10. 1940, Feb. 1.Deed. Lee & Vida Jacks to Margaret Jacks. Castro Adobe Lot.
  - 11. 1942, Oct. 31.Deed. MacIntoshes to Margaret & Vida Jacks. Palo Alto property. Includes corresp. with W.S. Griscom of Griscom & Co. & statement, title ins. prelim. report with diagram, Maurice D.L. Fuller, inventory.
  - 12. 1943, June 27.Letter of instructions - Margaret Jacks to Wells Fargo.
  - 13. 1944, Jan. 22.TDS Margaret Jacks re: Vida Jacks estate.
  - 14. 1944, Jan. 22.TDS Margaret Jacks re: Lee Jacks estate.
  - 15. 1954, Mar. -Nov.Papers re: gift of Pacific Bldg. to State Park Commission. Albert J. Callahan, Carmel Martin.
  - 16. 1954, June 29.Deed. M.A. Jacks to State of Calif., Pacific Bldg.
  - 17. 1954 -1959.Papers re: Gift of part of Rancho Los Coches to State - Stage Coach Inn (Oak Grove Adobe), roadside rest corresp., etc., deed (copy), map.
  - 18. 1960.Deed to safe at Casa del Oro. M.A. Jacks to State.
  - 19. 1960.Deeds. de Haven Painting Collection. M.A. Jacks to Monterey.
  - 20. n.d.Notes - offers made on land.
  - 21. n.d.Hand-drawn or traced map - San Vicente Rancho.
  - 22. Misc. cards showing rentals, notes held, etc.
- Margaret Jacks - Funeral (Box 5, Folder 76)
  Memorial contributions, etc., lists, notes. Monterey History & Art Assn. (Mayo Hayes O'Donnell), Mrs. Harry Kesterson (Woman's Club of Palo Alto), Harden Farms of Calif., Stanford Convalescent Home Senior Auxiliary, A. Florence Clayton.
- Margaret Jacks - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 77)
  Clips. -death of Will Jacks, activities of Romie C. Jacks; typed draft for article in Radcliffe Quarterly; typed typescript of interview (1953) given to Glenn S. Dumke re: David Jacks, etc.; typed genealogical record of Romie family; loose leaf address book; souvenir booklet on LaGranja.